I'm out here scrollin' and scrollin’
Scroll slow, homie
Tryna farm dopamine
you feel me?
But in truth and reality
I'm antisocial, cause I'm always
on social And I wanna feel social,
but I'm never really social
I'm antisocial, cause I'm always
on social Watchin' everybody glow
up, and I just wanna glow too
I'm antisocial, cause I'm always
on social Watchin' people vacate
to places I wanna go to
If it sounds like you, I guess I really
know you Even though I don't know you,
cause it's what I used to go through
Only way to beat it is to own
it So if you're gonna be here,
follow me to where the dough is
If you're here religiously, then
know this I can help you get more
conversions than the Pope did
Fo’ sho, kid!
Life is a blur when you start to
get motion That's why I offer
coaching to get you back focused
I’ll drop you a line if you write
a note below this And show you
the ropes before you get roped in
When I tell you what the fee is
You can love it, you can leave
it, as long as you believe
When I tell you what the fee is
You can love it, you can leave
it as long as you believe it
When I tell you what the fee is
You can love it, you can leave
it as long as you believe it
When I tell you what the fee is
You can love it, you can leave
it as long as you believe it
After a consultation, your team
gon' shine like a constellation
Profile optimization can turn
your hobby into an occupation
Stop the procrastination You keep
saying you gon' make content, make it
This could be a confirmation I ain't
no prophet, I just make em, look:
After a consultation, your team gon'
shine like a constellation yeah
Profile optimization can turn your
hobby into an occupation and….
Stop the procrastination You keep saying
one day you'll make the content, make it
This could be a confirmation I
ain't no prophet, I just make em go
When I tell you what the fee is
You can love it, you can leave
it as long as you believe it
When I tell you what the fee is
You can love it, you can leave
it as long as you believe it
When I tell you what the fee is
You can love it, you can leave
it as long as you believe it
When I tell you what the fee is
You can love it, you can leave
it as long as you believe it
When I tell you what the fee is
you can love it or just leave it
As long as you believe it
As long as you believe